Encounters are mysterious! But the world is even more so!
لقاءات البشر مغلّفة بالغموض، والعالم تلفّه طبقات أكثر حتّى
I'm so glad I'm with you!
!أنا مسرورٌ حقّاً لكوني معك
Today's stage is a white sandy beach! Couples come in varieties!
!مسرح اليوم هو شاطئ رمليّ أبيض !للأزواج أشكال متنوعة
He sees the single truth for what it is,
يرى الحقيقة الواحدة
and looks like a kid but has the mind of an adult!
يحمل مظهر طفل، لكنّ عقله عقل بالغ
His name? Detective Conan!
!اسمه المتحرّي كونان
Have you thought about it?
هل فكّرتِ بالأمر؟
Yeah. Saturday and Sunday.
أجل، السبت والأحد
Eh?! You will?! Really?! Thank you!
!ماذا؟ موافقة؟! حقّاً؟! شكراً لك
What're you doing this late at night?
ماذا تفعلين في هذا الوقت المتأخّر؟
Conan-kun!
!كونان-كن
Nothing! Just talking to a friend!
!لا شيء! كنت أكلّم صديقةً فقط
Alright, then! Goodnight!
!حسناً إذاً، عمتِ مساءً
Goodnight, Conan-kun!
!عمت مساءً يا كونان-كن
What's with her?
ما خطبها؟
Swimming in Izu?
سباحة في إيزو؟
Yeah! This Saturday and Sunday! You didn't have any plans!
!أجل السبت والأحد القادمين لم تكن لديك أيّة مخططات، صحيح
It's a really beautiful hotel and its private beach is the greatest!
إنّه فندق جميل جدّاً، وشاطئه الخاص !بغاية الروعة وفقما سمعت
I bet it costs the greatest, too.
لا بدّ أنّ تكلفته بغاية الارتفاع أيضاً
It's my first break in a while, so I'd rather drink and sleep here.
إنّها استراحتي الأولى منذ فترة، لذا أفضّل الشرب والنوم في المنزل
I'm pretty sure you drink and sleep even when you are working.
أنت تشرب وتنام حتّى عندما تعمل
But I already promised...
...لكنّي وعدتها سلفاً
Promised?
وعدتِها؟
With who?
من؟
Oh, no one! Nothing to do with you!
!لا شيء! كنتُ أكلّم نفسي
You want to come swimming too, right, Conan-kun?!
تريد الذهاب للسباحة أيضاً، صحيح يا كونان-كن؟
Right?!
!صحيح؟
Y-Yeah...
...أ-أجل
Forget it! Don't teach him to be lazy at such a young age!
كلا، لا ينفع! لا تعوديه على اللهو !في هذا السنّ الصغير
I hear the hotel's beach is filled with sexy women in swimsuits...
سمعتُ أنّ شاطئ ذاك الفندق مليء بنساء جذّابات في ملابس سباحة
It's brimming with college girls and female office workers!
!إنّه يعجّ بطالبات الجامعات والموظّفات المكتبيّات
What's she saying? Ran is usually against that kind of thing...
...ما الذي تقوله؟ ران في العادة تعارض
Well, I have been working a lot lately. Recuperation might be nice.
،حسناً، كنت غارقاً في الأعمال مؤخراً فلا ضير من النقاهة من حينٍ لآخر
Hurray! Thanks, Dad!
!رائع! شكراً لك يا أبي
No, it's nothing...
...لا، لا داعي
Hey, now! The old guy's the same as ever, but what's up with Ran?!
!مهلك! العمّ كعادته، لكن ما خطب ران؟
The sexy sea is calling for me!
!المحيط الجذّاب يناديني
Queen Hotel, Izu
فندق الملكة، إيزو
This hotel definitely lives up to its reputation.
هذا الفندق يرتقي لسمعته بالفعل
What is it? Are you looking for someone?
ما الأمر؟ أتبحثين عن أحد؟
Eh? Not at all!
ماذا؟ كلا
Dad! Let's hurry and check in!
!أبي! لنسرع ونسجّل دخولنا
Oh, right. We should hurry.
صحيح، علينا الإسراع
You've reserved two rooms.
حجزتما عرفتين، صحيح؟
Yes.
أجل
Huh? We don't need separate rooms. Wouldn't a suite be cheaper?
،ماذا؟ لسنا بحاجة لغرفتين منفصلتين ألن يكون الجناح أرخص؟
We'd only get in the way later on.
سنكون عقبة في تلك الحالة لاحقاً
Oh, nothing! Let's just change and hurry to the beach!
لا شيء! أكلّم نفسي! لنغيّر ثيابنا !سريعاً ونذهب للشاطئ
Yeah! Sexy girls are waiting!
!معكِ حقّ! فالفتيات الجذّابات بانتظاري
Too strange. Something is going on.
هذا غريب، هناك شيءٌ ما يجري بالتأكيد
So much sun!
!الكثير من الشمس
Tadah! Here it is, Dad! The swimsuit I bought yesterday!
مفاجأة! ها هو يا أبي! ثوب السباحة !الذي اشتريته بالأمس
What's that supposed to mean?
ما قصدك بذلك؟
Well, uhh, it means...
...حسناً، أعني
I can rub that oil on you if you'd like!
!يمكنني تدليكك بالوقاء الشمسيّ إذا أردتِ
E-Eri? Why are you here?
إ-إيري؟ لمَ أنتِ هنا؟
Why are you here?
...أنت... لمَ توجد
You're true lovebirds! It's like you make a perfect pair!
!أنتما زوجان هائمان بالحبّ حقّاً !تبدوان متناغمين
Ran, don't tell me...
...أيمكن أنّك يا ران
...you plotted this.
خطّطتِ لهذا؟
Eh? Plotted what?
ماذا؟ خطّطت لماذا؟
So that's why you got separate rooms?!
لذا حجزتِ غرفتين منفصلتين؟
Geez... it's so obvious.
يا إلهي، أمرك مكشوف
Come on, stop being angry, you two!
حاولا الابتهاج قليلاً
I apologize for secretly bringing you together!
أعتذر على ترتيب هذا سرّاً
Let's enjoy the Izu ocean more! Okay? Okay? Okay?!
!لنستمتع بمحيط إيزو أكثر !حسناً؟ حسناً؟ حسناً؟
I was enjoying it.
كنتُ أستمتع به
Until a hag showed up, wearing a swimsuit that didn't match her age.
حتّى ظهرت عجوز ترتدي ثوب سباحة لا يناسب عمرها
Oh, and who was drooling and howling at the sight of that hag?
عجباً، ومن طارت عيناه في تلك العجوز وحاول التودّد لها؟
Come on, you two...
...مـ-مهلكما
I gotta use the bathroom.
سأذهب للحمّام
Oh! Dad! Wait!
!أبي! انتظر
He's just embarrassed! He hasn't seen you in a while!
لعلّه محرج لا أكثر، فلم يرك منذ فترة
I wonder.
أشكّ في ذلك
To me, he looks like a petty-minded man who can't ever concede.
لا يبدو لي سوى رجل بسيط العقل لا يمكنه التنازل أبداً
Huh? You're not wearing your wedding ring? You usually do...
ماذا؟ لا ترتدين خاتم زواجك؟ مع أنّك تضعينه دوماً
Oh, it's on purpose. I was testing him to see if he'd notice.
أجل، كان ذلك عمداً
I thought there would still be hope if he noticed.
ظننتُ أنّه لو فعل، لربما بقي هناك أمل
I guess it was pointless.
يبدو أنّ الأمر كان بلا معنى
But that's...
...أخبرتك، ذلك
My life is a huge failure.
حياتي فشلٌ كبير
Maybe I should quit with this separation and start my life over.
ربما عليّ ترك هذه الحياة المنفصلة وبدء حياتي بمفردي من جديد
Mom!
!أمّي
Don't wind up like that man, Conan-kun.
إيّاك أن تصبح رجلاً مثله يا كونان-كن
O-Okay!
!حـ-حسناً
I don't think I would ever want to...
لا أظنّ أني سأصبح ولو أردت
What could've happened? Dad's been gone a long time.
ما الأمر؟ تأخّر أبي
He's probably back at the beach, hitting on girls.
لعلّه رجع للشاطئ وعاد للتقرّب من الفتيات
That's silly!
...لا يمكن
I'm so lucky to meet the great Mori Kogoro-san in a place like this!
لم يخطر لي أن ألتقي المتحرّي الشهير !موري كوغورو-سان في مكانٍ كهذا! يا لحظّي
It's an honor for me, too! To think I have such charming female fans!
الشرف لي، لم أتصوّر أن هناك فتاتين ساحرتين مثلكما معجبات لي
What did I tell you?
كما ظننت
It's just a coincidence!
!إنّها مصادفة
He probably just met them after he used the bathroom! And then--!
...لعلّه التقاهما في عودته من الحمّام! لذا
Look at his legs, then.
انظري لساقيه إذاً
They were clean before, but now there's sand up to his knees.
كانتا نظيفتين قبل قليل، لكن يكسوهما الرمل حتّى ركبتيه الآن
I can easily imagine him kneeling in the sand to rub oil on them.
يمكنني تخيّله وهو يركع في الرمل لتدليكهما بالواقي الشمسي
I wonder if he brought them here to show off to me.
هل جلبهما إلى هنا كي يستعرض أمامي يا ترى؟
What a pathetic man.
يا للرجل السخيف
You can't be serious...
...لا يمكن
Don't tell me he actually--!
...أيمكن أنّ العمّ حقّاً
Maybe I should start a fan club or something!
!ربما عليّ فتح نادي معجبين
Never mind.
نعم، يمكن
Hey! Dad!
!لحظة! أبي
Oh, Ran! These girls say they're fans of mine!
ران! تقول هاتان الفتاتان أنّهما من معجباتي
Let me introduce the family.
سأعرفكما على العائلة
Urgh! Whatever!
يا إلهي، لا علاقة لي
I'll start with these two first! I met them on the beach just now!
سأبدأ بهاتين، التقيتهما على الشاطئ قبل قليل
Toda Kiwako, College Student
تودا كيواكو طالبة جامعية
This is Toda Kiwako-san, a college student.
تودا كيواكو-سان، طالبة جامعية
Hello!
مرحباً
And then Matsuzaki Harumi-san,
ورفيقتها
Matsuzaki Harumi, College Student
ماتسوزاكي هارومي، طالبة جامعية
also a college student.
ماتسوزاكي هارومي-سان، طالبة جامعية أيضاً
Nice to meet you!
!سُررنا بلقائكم
Oh! How cute! Is this your son?
يا لظرافته! أهو ابنك؟
No, that's Conan, an acquaintance's kid who we're looking after.
لا، إنّه ابن أحد معارفنا الذي نعتني به، اسمه كونان
Behind him is my daughter, Ran.
وخلفه ابنتي ران
Hi.
مرحباً
And in the back is...
...ومن في الخلف
...his ex-wife, Eri.
زوجته السابقة، إيري
Eh? You're divorced?
ماذا؟ أنتِ مطلّقة؟
No, she's just joking!
!لا، إنّها تمزح فحسب
No, not necessarily...
...لا، ليس بالضرورة
Knock that off, old man!
!أنت، أيّها المُسن
Kawazu Kunio, College Student
رجل في عمرك عليه !ألّا يعبث مع رفاقي
A guy your age shouldn't be messin' with my friends!
كاوازو كونيو طالب جامعيّ
Hey! Masahiko! You say somethin', too!
!ماساهيكو! قل شيئاً بدورك
Your dear fiancée and sister are bein' fooled, you know!
فخطيبتك وأختك العزيزتين تحت تلاعبه
Now, now. You don't have to be so angry.
هوّن عليك، لا داعي لتغضب هكذا
Matsuzaki Masahiko, College Student
ماتسوزاكي ماساهيكو طالب جامعيّ
Besides, he seems to be a celebrity, so you can't blame them.
،كما يبدو أنّه شخصيّة مشهورة فلا يمكنك لومهما
Celebrity?
شخصية مشهورة؟
He's Mori Kogoro-san, the famous "Sleeping Kogoro" detective!
إنّه المتحرّي الشهير موري كوغورو-سان !المعروف بكوغورو النائم
I knew it! I knew I recognized you from somewhere!
!كما ظننت! بدا لي أنّي رأيتك قبلاً
I'm that well-known? I'm at a loss for words!
...أأنا معروفٌ لهذا الحدّ حقّاً؟ لا أجد التعابير
My face gets in papers and on TV all over, so I can't do anything bad.
،وجهي يظهر في الصحف وعلى التلفاز فلا أستطيع الإقدام على شيءٍ سيّئ
Say, have you had lunch yet?
أخبرني، هل تناولت الغداء؟
No.
ليس بعد
Then let's all have lunch together!
!لنتناوله معاً إذاً
There's a small restaurant behind this hotel. What do you say?
يوجد مطعم صغير وراء هذا الفندق، ما رأيكم؟
Oh! Sounds good!
!فكرة حسنة
Let's go!
!لنذهب
Oh, you're all part of your school's scuba diving club?
أنتم أعضاء في نادي غوص السكوبا في جامعتكم إذاً؟
Yes, we even had a dive this morning before lunch!
أجل، ذهبنا للغوص قبل الغداء هذا الصباح أيضاً
So this is your last time diving single before the wedding next week?
أي كان ذلك غوصكما الأخير كأعزبين قبل الزواج الأسبوع القادم؟
No, we'll be diving tomorrow too, so this isn't the last time.
،كلا، سنذهب للغوص غداً أيضاً فليست المرّة الأخيرة
But it was tough getting my brother into this club! He can't swim!
لكن كان ضمّ أخي لهذا النادي صعباً بما أنّه لا يجيد السباحة
He can't swim?
لا يجيد السباحة؟
Right.
أجل
You don't need to swim to dive. You got an oxygen tank, after all.
لا تحتاج لإتقان السباحة للغوص، فمعك أسطوانة أكسجين
Even as a boy, Masahiko-san was never able to swim.
حتّى أثناء صغره، كان ماساهيكو-سان لا يجيد السباحة أبداً
Quit it...
أوقفي ذلك
Eh?! Does that mean you two are childhood friends?!
ماذا؟ أثناء صغره؟ أيعني ذلك أنّكما صديقا طفولة؟
Oh, I suppose...
...أجل، صحيح
Wow! Childhood friends getting married!
!رائع! زواج صديقَي طفولة
It's almost like my mom and dad!
!مثل أبي وأمّي
Right?! Right?! Right?!
!صحيح؟ صحيح؟ صحيح؟
"Childhood friends," huh...
...صديقَي طفولة إذاً
So many a couple have been heartbroken by that sweet phrase...
كم تستدرج هذه العبارة الحلوة ...من دموع أزواج
Embracing familiar friend and fantasy is the height of foolishness.
اعتناق مبدأ الصديق القريب والخيالات من أكبر أشكال السذاجة
Well, I don't think you'll need it,
حسناً، لا أظنّكما ستحتاجان
but if you ever distrust your wife, just call the Mori Detective Agency.
لكن إذا شككت بزوجتك يوماً، فلتتّصل بوكالة موري للتحرّي فحسب
If you want to receive major compensation from your husband
إذا أردتِ تلقّي تعويض ماليّ كبير من زوجك عند الطلاق
when you divorce, just call the Kisaki Law Office.
فلتتّصلي بمكتب كيساكي للقانون
Call anytime!
!في خدمتك
Brrr...
...بارد
How did it turn out this way?
كيف آل الأمر لهذا؟
Come to think of it, where's your other childhood friend?
بالمناسبة، أين صديق طفولتك الآخر؟
Snore-killing?
الغوص السطحيّ؟
Diving without an air tank.
إنّه الغوص دون أسطوانة هواء
He's diving without even eating?
يغوص دون الأكل حتّى؟
Yes, he is kind of strange; he likes the ocean more than women!
،أجل، إنّه غريب أطوار نوعاً ما ويحبّ المحيط أكثر من النساء
Wonder if he plans to marry a shark!
هل سيتزوّج قرشاً يا ترى؟
That's mean!
!ذلك قاسٍ
Hey, Harumi.
اسمعي يا هارومي
Sorry to ask, but could you get a fresh beach towel from our room?
أعتذر على الطلب، لكن أيمكنك جلب منشفة شاطئ جديدة من غرفتنا؟
Hey, Kiwako. Don't tell me you're going to...
...كيواكو، أستذهبين الآن لـ
Yep! I suddenly want to take a dip in the ocean, too!
أجل، راودتني رغبة بالغوص في المحيط فجأةً
Will you be alright drunk?
أستكونين بخير وأنت ثملة؟
You don't have to do it today. Can't you go tomorrow?
ليس عليكِ فعلها اليوم، ألا تؤجلينها للغد؟
I'll be fine! I haven't had that much to drink!
!سأكون بخير! فلم أشرب لذاك الحدّ
It'll just be some light snorkeling!
سيكون غطساً سطحياً خفيفاً
Should I join you, then?
هل أرافقك إذاً؟
That's okay! I want to dive by myself!
!لا داعي! أريد الغوص بمفردي
Later, Harumi! Don't forget!
!إلى اللقاء يا هيرومي! أعتمد عليك
Kiwako...
...كيواكو
The ocean seems to be getting rough.
يبدو أنّ أمواج المحيط تشتدّ
I wonder if Kiwako is okay...
هل ستكون كيواكو بخير؟
Oh, you're all here!
!أنتم مجتمعون هنا
Hiroshi! You're with Kawazu?
هيروشي! أنت مع كاوازو؟
We ran into each other in the john.
التقينا بعضنا في دورة المياه قبل قليل
Ito Hiroshi, College Student
إيتو هيروشي طالب جامعي
Today's diving spot was really great!
!كانت نقطة غوص اليوم ممتازة حقّاً
Huh? Where's your bride?
ماذا؟ أين عروسك؟
Still in the ocean.
لا تزال في البحر
Huh? You didn't see her?
ماذا؟ لم تقابلها؟
No, not at all.
كلا، البتّة
Look! There she is! She's waving to us!
!انظروا! ها هي! إنّها تلوّح لنا
Kiwako!
!كيواكو
Something doesn't seem right!
!هنالك أمرٌ غريب
Wait!
!أيمكن؟
She's drowning!
!تغرق
K-Kiwako!
!كـ-كيواكو
Wait!
!أيمكن؟
She's drowning!
!تغرق
K-Kiwako!
!كـ-كيواكو
Kiwako!
!كيواكو
Brother!
!أخي
Wait! Masahiko!
!انتظر! ماساهيكو
Kiwako!
!كيواكو
You idiot! Get back! You can't swim!
!يا أحمق
You're alright now!
!أنتِ بخيرٍ الآن
Kiwako! Stay calm!
!كيواكو! اهدئي
Where's Masahiko-san?
أين ماساهيكو-سان؟
Yeah, he's here. He came to save you.
إنّه هنا، أتى لإنقاذك
Oh... That's a relief...
هكذا إذاً... حمداً لله
W-What was that?
ما-ما كان ذلك؟
T-That's--!
...تـ-تلك
Okay, stud! You can carry her now!
هاك أيّها العشيق، يمكنك حملها
Don't worry, Masahiko! She probably just had a leg cramp!
لا تقلق يا ماساهيكو، لا بدّ أنّ ساقها تشنّجت فسقطت لا أكثر
Sea snake!
!أفعى بحر
D-Don't tell me she--!
...أ-أيمكن
Sheesh. We told you not to go out there.
يا إلهي، لذا أخبرناك ألّا تذهبي
Now, now. You can argue all you want after you're married.
هوّن عليك، يمكنكما تأجيل الجدال الزوجيّ لبعد الزواج
Hey, Kiwako. Are you listening?
كيواكو، أتسمعينني؟
K-Kiwako!
!كـ-كيواكو
What's going on?! What happened?!
ما الأمر؟ ما الذي يجري؟
Hey! Say something! Hey!
!أنت! تمالكي نفسك! أنت
Don't move her!
!لا تحرّكوها
She might've been bitten by a sea snake!
!ربما عضّتها أفعى بحر
A sea snake?!
!أفعى بحر؟
There was a sea snake right by us earlier!
!كانت هناك أفعى بحر قبل قليل بقربنا
I-If so, then there should be fang marks somewhere!
فـ-في تلك الحالة، لا بدّ من وجود آثار أنياب بمكانٍ ما
H-Hand... Left hand...
...يدي... يدي اليسرى
Her left hand!
يدها اليسرى
There they are! Bite marks!
!ها هي! آثار عضّ
Then she was bitten by a sea snake?!
عضّتها أفعى بحر بالفعل إذاً؟
For now, we have to tie off the affected area and suck out the poison!
علينا ربط منطقة العضّ للوقت الراهن وامتصاص السمّ
Does anyone have anything to use as a tourniquet?!
ألا يملك أحدكم ما يمكن الربط به؟
Will a handkerchief do?!
أسيفي المنديل بالغرض؟
Alright!
!حسناً
But how did you know it was a sea snake, little--?
لكن كيف عرفت أنّها أفعى بحر يا فتى؟
Hey! Little boy!
!مهلك! يا فتى
What's with him?
ما خطبه؟
I saw the sea snake! It was about forty centimeters long!
أنا من رأت أفعى البحر، أظنّ طولها كان بقرابة 40 سنتيمتراً
What's wrong?!
ما الخطب؟
Call an ambulance, quick!
!اطلبي الإسعاف فوراً
What? I thought you saved her from drowning?
ماذا؟ ظننت أنّكم أنقذتموها من الغرق
A sea snake bit Kiwako-san on the back of her hand!
عضّت أفعى بحر كيواكو-سان !على كفّ يدها
A sea snake?!
!أ-أفعى بحر؟
Whoa! Those are really poisonous!
!سمّ تلك شديدٌ جدّاً
So hurry and call an ambulance!
!لذا اتّصلوا بالإسعاف فوراً
H-Hey!
!مـ-مهلك
Why'd he just run off with iced tea?
لمَ أخذ الشاي المثلج وركض هكذا؟
Tannin.
التانين
Washing the wound with the tannin in tea to neutralize the poison
غسل الجرح بالتانين في الشاي لمكافحة السمّ
is the best emergency measure for sea snake bites.
هو أفضل إسعاف أوليّ طارئ لعضّات أفعى البحر
Of course, the person who sucks out the poison
على الشخص الذي يمتصّ السم غسل فمه
will need to wash their mouth with tea, too.
بالشاي أيضاً بالطبع
But how does that runt know that?
لكن لمَ يعرف ذاك الفتى ذلك؟
Oh? He's a pretty sharp boy.
إنّه صبيّ فطن
He's much more useful than we are, as we twiddle our thumbs here.
أكثر فائدةً منّا بكثير نحن من نجلس متلاعبين بإبهامنا ونراقب فحسب
Though shouldn't you ask why a certain former police detective
أليست المشكلة بالأحرى عدم معرفة
didn't know about it instead?
محقّق شرطة سابق لتلك المعلومة؟
In any case, I'll call the ambulance.
سأتّصل بالإسعاف بأيّ حال
You go ask the cook for some coarse tea full of tannin.
اطلب من الطاهي تجهيز شاي أخضر مليء بالتانين
I'm counting on you, Great Detective.
أعتمد عليك أيّها المتحرّي العظيم
Kiwako... Hang in there!
!كيواكو... تماسكي
I'm her fiancé. Can I come with her?
أنا خطيبها، أيمكنني مرافقتكم في العربة؟
Of course.
تفضّل
Who saw the sea snake?!
!من رأى أفعى البحر؟
I did!
كانت أنا
Do you know what type it was?!
هل عرفتِ صنفها؟
The type?
صنفها؟
There's a picture book in the hotel office...
يوجد كتاب مصوّر في مكتب الفندق
Then contact the hospital as soon as you know what kind it was!
اتّصلي بالمشفى حالما تعرفين ذلك إذاً
Right!
!حاضر
Office
المكتب
This is it! It was this sea snake!
!كانت هذه! أفعى البحر هذه بلا شكّ
A black-banded sea krait!
أفعى البحر المخطّطة السوداء السامة
What's it doing in Izu?
لمَ توجد في إيزو؟
They sometimes show up on the Kuroshio Current.
تأتي هنا أحياناً على تيّار كوروشيو
There's just a prickly feeling and then no swelling after that,
تشعر بوخز فحسب بعد عضّتها، ولا تورّم هناك
so some fishermen have died without ever noticing them.
فمات صيّادون دون الانتباه لها وفقما سمعت
You let people swim in the ocean with such dangerous sea snakes?!
تفتحون الشاطئ رغم وجود !أفاعي بحر خطيرة كهذه؟
N-No!
!كـ-كلا
The fishermen just happened to be bitten
في حالة الصيّاد، صادف أنّه تعرّض للعضّ
when sticking their hands in fish nets that had also caught the snakes!
بعدما أدخل يده في شبكة الصيد التي اصطادت أفاعٍ
Even so, we're talking about sea snakes here!
!لكن، هذه أفاعي البحر
Surely some might suddenly attack people!
!لا بدّ أنّ هناك حالات تهاجم البشر فيها فجأةً
These snakes are docile and never attack people on their own.
تلك الأفاعي هادئة، ولا تهاجم البشر من تلقاء أنفسها
In the twenty-two years since this hotel was founded,
،في الاثنين وعشرين عاماً مذ تأسيس الفندق
not a single visitor has been bitten by one.
لم يتعرّض أيّ نزيل للعضّ من قبلها
Umm, do any of these sea snakes have wings?
المعذرة، أتملك بعض أفاعي البحر هذه أجنحة؟
Wings? No such variety exists.
أجنحة؟ لا يوجد صنف كذاك
That's strange.
هذا غريب
I recall seeing small wings behind the head of the one I saw...
أتذكّر رؤية أجنحة صغيرة وراء رأس التي رأيتها
Seaweed or something must've caught onto it.
لا بدّ أنّ طحلباً بحرياً علق بها وما شابه
I guess...
...ربما ذلك
But only my daughter could remember so much from one quick look!
لكن تذكّرك لكلّ ذلك بنظرة !سريعة يثبت أنّكِ ابنتي فعلاً
I only remember well because it was so shocking!
علق الأمر بذاكرتي لأنّه كان صادماً لا أكثر
Yes, you have a wonderful power of observation!
قوّة ملاحظتك مبهرة بالفعل
Unlike a certain someone else
بخلاف أحدهم الذي لم يلحظ
who didn't even notice his wife's missing wedding ring.
خاتم زواج زوجته المفقود حتّى
Huh? What about your ring now?
ماذا؟ ماذا قلتِ عن خاتمك؟
Nothing.
لا شيء
I can only imagine she playfully stuck her hand in the snake's nest.
كلّ ما يتراءى لي أنّ كيواكو أدخلت يدها في وكر الأفعى عبثاً
Yeah.
أجل
In any case, I'll go contact the hospital!
سأتّصل بالمشفى بأيّ حال
No, that's not it!
لا، ليس صحيحاً
Those fang marks were no accident!
لم تكن آثار الأنياب تلك حادثاً
Someone held the snake and forced it to bite her hand in the water!
كان أحدهم يحملها، وأجبرها على عضّ !يد كيواكو-سان في الماء
In which case, was it one of the people who rushed to help her?!
مما يعني أنّه أحد الذين هرعوا لنجدتها؟
No, everyone was empty-handed then,
كلا، كان الجميع خاويي الأيدي وقتها
and they rushed there because Kiwako-san was drowning!
واندفعوا لها لأنّ كيواكو-سان كانت تغرق
There's no one crazy enough to have a sea snake ready
لا يوجد شخص أحمق يحضر أفعى بحر معه
when they don't know if someone will drown or not!
وهو لا يعلم حتّى إذا كان هدفه سيغرق أم لا
It'd be more natural to think she started to drown after she was bitten.
من المنطقيّ أكثر التفكير بأنّها بدأت الغرق بعد تعرّضها للعضّ
Which means only Hiroshi-san could've done it!
مما يعني أنّ الوحيد القادر على ارتكاب الجريمة كان هيروشي-سان
He was in the ocean just before she drowned,
كان في المحيط قبيل غرقها
so he could've had it bite her!
!فاستطاع جعلها تعضّها
But his emergency treatment afterward was perfect.
لكنّ علاجه الأوليّ بعد اكتشافنا لعضّة الأفعى كان مثالياً
Would someone go that far to help someone they're trying to kill?
هل سيبذل كلّ ذلك لمساعدة الشخص الذي حاول قتله لو كان الفاعل؟
In any event, one of those four people was responsible for this!
أيّاً يكن، الفاعل هو أحد الأربعة الذين !كانوا متواجدين هناك آنذاك
You liked Kiwako-san?
كنت تحبّ كيواكو-سان؟
I guess it was love at first sight.
أظنّه كان حبّاً من النظرة الأولى
Can you help me? I can't find Kiwako's insurance card!
ساعدني بأيّ حال، لا أجد بطاقة تأمين كيواكو
Inside the towel at the bottom of the bag.
داخل المنشفة في أسفل الحقيبة
This was no accident! And you're the one behind it!
!لم تكن هذه حادثة، والفاعل كان أنت
On the next Conan--
في الحلقة القادمة من كونان
“The Scuba Diving Murder Case (Part 2).”
جريمة قتل غوص السكوبا (الجزء الثاني)
Next Conan's hint:
تلميح الحلقة القادمة
Ring.
خاتم
Next episode is part two. Who's the culprit?
الحلقة القادمة هي الجزء الثاني، من الفاعل؟
A hotel employee.
!مسؤول الفندق
Why me?
!لمَ أنا؟